Guide to the Vassar College Buildings and Grounds Files, 1879-2007 (bulk 1910-2000)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Price Changes – Hess, 1987 (Box 61)
- IBM – Poughkeepsie Management Institute Conferences, 1987 (Box 61)
- ID System, 1989 (Box 61)
- Infra-Red Surveys, 1986 (Box 61)
- Loss Prevention Surveys – IRI, 1986 (Box 61)
- Oil Inventories – 1986/1987 (Box 61)
- Paging Systems, 1986 (Box 61)
- Pest Control, 1985-1987 (Box 61)
- Power Department, 1983-1988 (Box 61)
- Project Lists – 1986-1987 (Box 61)
- Carriage Hill Property – Adjoining V.C. on Route 376, 1967-1987 (Box 61)
- Property Tax Exemptions – 1987 (Box 61)
- Property Tax Exemptions – 1986 (Box 61)
- Collegeview Avenue Fence Line, 1970-1980 (Box 61)
- Property – General, 1954-1988 (Box 61)
- Property – Available for Lease or Purchase by Vassar College, 1965-1982 (Box 61)
- Refrigeration Equipment – Contract, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
- Reunion 1987 (Box 61)
- Facilities Operations Staff Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
- Design of Storm Sewer System, 1986 (Box 61)
- Summer Programs ’88, 1988 (Box 61)
- Summer Programs ’89, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
- Summer Projects – 1986 (Box 61)
- Summer Programs, 1986-1988 (Box 61)
- THERM, 1986 (Box 61)
- Trash Collection – 1986-1988 (Box 61)
- Tricentennial Celebration – 1987 (Box 61)
- Uniforms, 1987 (Box 61)
- United Way – 1985, 1986-1988 (Box 61)
- Road Repairs – 1985 – 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
- United Way ’89, 1989 (Box 61)
- Vassar Lake – 1987, 1986 (Box 61)
- Vendors, 1985-1987 (Box 61)
- Wetlands, 1987 (Box 61)
- Winter Curtailment 88/89, 1988 (Box 61)
- Winter Weekend 88/89, 1988 (Box 61)
- Winter Weekend – 1988 (Box 61)
- Winter Break Curtailment – 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
- Loeb Art Center Project Manual Vol. I, 1991 (Box 62)
- Loeb Art Center Project Manual Vol. II, 1991 (Box 62)
- Loeb Art Center Project Manual Vol. III, 1991 (Box 62)
- [College Center Addendums], 1973-1977 (Box 62)
- Library Progress Photographs, 1961-1972 (Box 62)
- [Electrical Drawings HVAC] (Box 62)
- [Electrical Drawings], 1976 (Box 62)
- Vassar College Electrical Interconnection Diagrams Ansul Job No. 7255, 1975-1976 (Box 62)
- [Vassar Library Sprinkler System], 1975 (Box 62)
- [Vassar College Library Circuit Breaker Instruction Manual], 1976 (Box 62)
- Library Addition – The Design Decision Making Process by Judith E. Schwartz, 1976 (Box 62)
- Mudd – Punch Lists 1987-1988, 1987-1990 (Box 62)
- S.G. Mudd Chemistry, 1985-1986 (Box 62)
- Project Expenditures, 1987 (Box 62)
- Mudd Air Conditioner, 1988 (Box 62)
- Mudd Building – Flack and Kurtz, 1987-1988 (Box 62)
- S.G. Mudd – Addendums 1, 2, 3, 1982 (Box 62)
- Chemistry Building – 1 May 1982 – Dec 1983, 1982-1985 (Box 62)
- Chemistry Building – Jan 1981 – 30 Apr 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 62)
- Chemistry Building Study Dec 1980 (Box 62)
- S.G. Mudd – Concrete and Soil Testing, 1982-1983 (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd Chemistry- Compressed Air Services, 1984 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Blinds and Shades, 1984 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Blueprint Transmittals, 1982-1984 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Door Alarm System, 1984-1985 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Electric – Underground Street Light Wiring (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd Chemistry – Electric, 1984-1986 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Energy Management System, 1984 (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd – Emergency Generator and Electric (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd Chemistry – Elevator, 1985 (Box 63)
- Equipment Schedule – Mudd Chemistry Building (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Fire and Temperature Alarm System, 1984-1985 (Box 63)
- Chemistry – Finish Hardware, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd Chemistry – Floor Plans, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Equipment and Furnishings, 1984 (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd Chemistry – HVAC and Plumbing, 1983-1985 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – HVAC Building Services, Alarm System, 1985 (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd Chemistry – Punch Lists and Construction Reports, 1984-1988 (Box 63)
- HVAC – Mudd – Valve Charts (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – HVAC Temperature Controls, 1984 (Box 63)
- Renewal Parts Proposal, 1984 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Equipment Specifications, 1982 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Landscaping, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
- S.G. Chemistry – Metal Panel Color Selection, 1983 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Meters (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Moving Expenses, 1984 (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd Facility – Photos (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd – Problem File, 1985 (Box 63)
- Chemistry – Roofing, 1983-1987 (Box 63)
- Chemistry – Shop Drawing Schedules, 1983 (Box 63)
- Chemistry – Sprinkler System, 1983 (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd Chemistry – Steam System, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
- S.G. Mudd Building – Steel Testing, 1983 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Telephones, 1983-1985 (Box 63)
- Chemistry Building – Job Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry Building – Change Orders, 1982-1983 (Box 63)
- Payments to Contractor, 1983-1985 (Box 63)
- Mudd Chemistry – Change Proposals, 1983 (Box 63)
- Chemistry Building – Payment to Architects, 1986 (Box 63)
- Chemistry Building – Payments to Engineer, 1981 (Box 63)
- Chemistry – Sub-contracts, 1983 (Box 63)
- Chemistry – Building Contracts, 1982 (Box 63)
- Asbestos – M.H., 1987 (Box 63)
- Chicago Basement, 1987-1988 (Box 63)
- ECM VIII [Energy Conservation Measure] Grant Reports, 1986-1987; (2 folders) (Box 64)
- ECM VIII [Energy Conservation Measure] – Bids, 1986 (Box 64)
- [Brand / Biscraft Asbestos Abatement Bid for Sanders Chemistry Building], 1987 (Box 64)
- [Quadrangle Landscaping Re-design – Master Plans, Minutes, Project Expenditures and Correspondence], 1986-1990; (10 folders) (Box 64)
- Walker Field House [Correspondence and furnishings], 1983-1986 (Box 64)
- Athletic Facility [Walker Field House] – Certificates of Completion, 1982 (Box 64)
- Athletic Facility [Walker Field House] – Gym Floor, 1982, 1988; (2 folders) (Box 64)
- Walker Field House [General Correspondence], 1982 (Box 64)
- [Walker Field House] – H.W.R. System-Zoning, 1985 (Box 64)
- Walker Field House Swimming Pool, 1981-1986 (Box 64)
- Athletic Facility [Walker Field House] – Payments to Contractor, 1981-1982 (Box 64)
- Athletic Facility [Walker Field House] – Electrical Shop Drawings, 1981-1983 (Box 64)
- Proposed Physical Education Facilities [Correspondence and proposals], 1976-1979 (Box 64)
- Athletic Facility [Walker Field House] – Punch List, 1982-1983 (Box 64)
- [Mudd Chemistry Building – Floor Plans and Meeting Minutes], 1982-1984 (Box 64)
- Mudd Chemistry Building – Contract Documents [Outside Air Plenum, Railings and Doors], 1982 (Box 65)
- Seeley G Mudd Chemistry Building – Plant Operations, 1982 (Box 65)
- Proposed D.C. to A.C. Conversion, Burns and Roe Inc. [Sketches and Plans], 1955; (2 folders) (Box 65)
- Evaluation of Asbestos Control Requirements, Vassar College, 1986 (Box 65)
- Vassar College Asbestos Survey and Assessment Report, 1986 (Box 65)
- Project Manual – Asbestos Abatement, 1986 (Box 65)
- Project Manual – Energy Conservation Modifications – Vassar College, 1986; (2 folders) (Box 65)
- Updated Detailed Energy Analysis, Main Building [Superceded], 1984 (Box 65)
- Project Manual – Energy Conservation Modifications at the Main Building [Final Review Set], 1985; (3 folders) (Box 65)
- Energy Conservation Modifications – [Plans and Sketches] (Box 65)
- Specifications for the Construction of Experimental Theatre, Vassar College (Box 65)
- Vassar College Computer Center [Mechanical], 1966 (Box 65)
- Vassar College Computer Center – [Johnson Control Condensed Catalogue and plans], 1966 (Box 65)
- Biological Sciences Building – General Document 1, 1971 (Box 65)
- Boots and Saddle Club [Executed License Agreement, Public Liability Insurance Certificate and associated correspondence], 1959-1964 (Box 65)
- Special Committee on Dining Facilities, October 1, 1964 (Box 65)
- College Center- Addendum Number 1 to the Specifications and Drawings [Office Copy], 1973 (Box 65)
- Plant Operations and Addenda 1-5, 1971 (Box 65)
- Specifications- Additions to the Electric Distribution System and other utilities for Vassar College, 1971 (Box 65)
- Sanders Classroom Building- General Construction Work Specifications, 1987; (2 folders) (Box 65)
- Sanders Classroom Building- Mechanical and Electrical Specifications, 1987 (Box 65)
- Specifications – Biological Sciences Building, Divisions 6-16 (Box 66)
- Computer Center – Drawings, 1966 (Box 66)
- Language Center Specifications [2 copies], 1957; (2 folders) (Box 66)
- Contract Documents and Specifications to an All College Dining Hall for Vassar College [2 copies], 1971 (Box 66)
- Vassar Computer Center Fire Protection Equipment Manual, 1966 (Box 66)
- [Elevator Specifications and Drawings], 1925; (2 folders) (Box 66)
- Proposed Changes to the Mechanical Plant at Vassar College, 1916 (Box 66)
- [Professor Abbey Leach House- Specifications, photocopy], ca. 1910 (Box 66)
- Specifications for the Drama Workshop, Vassar College, [Copy 1], 1972 (Box 66)
- Vassar College Residences-Specifications Addendum Two, 1971 (Box 67)
- All College Dining Hall – Daily Records, July 1, 1971 to June 1, 1973, 1971-1973; (2 folders) (Box 67)
- All College Dining Hall Plumbing Details, 1971, 1973-1974; (2 folders) (Box 67)
- Addendum Number 1 to the Contract Documents and Specifications to an All College Dining Hall for Vassar College, 1971 (Box 67)
- [College Dining Hall Plans and Drawings], 1971-1973; (2 folders) (Box 67)
- [College Dining Hall] - Electrical, 1971 (Box 67)
- [College Dining Hall] – Sprinkler, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
- HVAC [College Dining Hall], 1971-1973 (Box 67)
- Behind the Scenes in the Bookshop – Marion Bacon (Box 67)
- Chimney By Alphons Custodis, Erected 1908 [Plans] (Box 67)
- Boiler House and Boiler Data [Plans], 1933 (Box 67)
- Boiler House Number 5 – Babcock and Wilcox Co. 1921 Construction [Plans] (Box 67)
- Setting Piping Plan for Tubular Boilers, 1923 (Box 67)
- Motor Driven Traveling Crane With Grab Bucket Hoist [Plans], 1921 (Box 67)
- Boiler House Layout as of 1928 (Box 67)
- Grounds – Map Showing Locations of Roads, Walks, etc. As Per Survey Dated July 30, 1926 (Box 68)
- Drawing – Main Building Basement [Copy], 1968 (Box 68)
- Specifications and Report – Bludworth Voice Amplifier System, Belle Skinner Music Building, 1930 (Box 68)
- Specifications – House for Miss Claudia Lyon, 1949 (Box 68)
- Specifications – Steam Distribution System Renovations Phase IV, 1968 (Box 68)
- HVAC Valve Identification Chart, ca. 1970 (Box 68)
- 1985-1986 Water Shutdown (Box 68)
- Vassar College Chemistry Building – Design Development Specifications, 1981 (Box 68)
- Loeb Art Center - Requests For Information Log, 1991-1993; (2 folders) (Box 68)
- Loeb Art Center – Punch list, 1992-1993 (Box 68)
- Chapel – Roof Repairs & Rehabilitation July 2, 1952 – June 26, 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 68)
- Mudd Chemistry – Electrical Pull Sheets, 1984; (2 folders) (Box 68)
- Fiberboard Plans – College Center (Box 68)
- Faculty Housing Sites – Triangulated Executed Contract Documents [Receipts], 1965 (Box 68)
- Vassar College - Distribution System Phase III, 1957 (Box 68)
- Vassar College – Distribution System Phase IV [Equipment Contracts and Plans], 1958, 1971 (Box 68)
- Specifications – Dr. W.B. Hill [Faculty Housing] (Box 68)
- Specifications for the Drama Workshop, Vassar College, [Copy 2], 1972 (Box 68)
- All College Dining Hall Sketches, 1971 (Box 68)
- Vassar College Facilities Inventory Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 69)
- Vassar College Facilities Inventory Reports, 1971,1973 (Box 70)
- Fire escape plans (Boxes 71-72)
- Photographs (Boxes 73-76)
- Miscellaneous oversized material (Box 77)
- Science Facilities Project - Polshek Partnership Portfolio, 2007 (Box 78)
- Science Facilities Project - List of other considered portfolios, 2007 (Box 78)